Contact

9130451715 (Home) ravigangawane04@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ravigangawane (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

angular 7 Bootstrap Web Development

Ravi Gangawane

Software Engineer at Cybage Software Private Limited Kalyaninagar, Pune

Pune

Summary

Highly motivated IT professional with extensive experience 3 years in web development Angular, JavaScript, HTML5, Bootstrap4, Jquery, Materialize, MDBoostrap, NgBoostrap, CSS3, Less, SASS, SCSS Angular Material.

Worked on multiple projects simultaneously. Leading a team of developers to provide clarity, ensure progress towards goals and conducting informal code reviews.

Collaborate with Product Management to understand business requirements and design appropriate solutions.

Troubleshooting and Problem-solving skills and the ability to learn and adopt new technologies.

Working knowledge in GIT, NPM, Grunt, Gulp, Yeoman, Web pack Familiarity with Agile Development(SCRUM), Redmine, Trello

Experience

Cybage Software Software Engineer September 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Kalyaninagar Pune

MeLayer Software Solutions LLP Web Developer January 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 8 months)

4th Floor, Bandal Capital, Paud road, Near Kothrud Bus Depot., Kothrud Pune

Mahatma phule Madhyamic Vidhyalaya, Lavale Teacher January 2015 - December 2016 (2 years)

Education

Pune District Education Mandals Arts, Science & Commerce College, Pirangut, Tal.Mulshi, Dist. Pune BCA, Computer Science · (2011 - 2014)